{
    "id": "ef6c546ace2c4ed48e7b0a36bbe1744f",
    "title": "Word Forms Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "The verb form of ‘note’ is",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "notify",
                "notification",
                "noticeable"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "3c7f8ff0230f4c2eaa04e753f4219425"
        },
        {
            "question": "The adjective form of ‘black’ is",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "blacken",
                "blackish",
                "blacked"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "d56512f096eb427c9863b00ce32e31d1"
        },
        {
            "question": "The adjective form of ‘courage’ is",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "courageous",
                "courageously",
                "courageousness"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "fc600c6c533c4aee8bd3db20c04ae839"
        },
        {
            "question": "The adjective form of ‘ease’ is",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "easy",
                "easiness",
                "uneasy"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "3e0dcc99824c41bd98d543cb8239eece"
        },
        {
            "question": "The verb form of ‘tireless’ is",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "tired",
                "tire",
                "tiresome"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "15cde7327e4d4b1daeb0bb695df6e1fb"
        },
        {
            "question": "The adjective form of ‘heaven’ is",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "heave",
                "heavenly",
                "hellish"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "b0f5b75da16b4f9ab2c3a2420fd8090d"
        },
        {
            "question": "The adjective form of ‘talk’ is",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "talking",
                "talked",
                "talkative"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "fc6fd96fa25845659bae0941765aae07"
        },
        {
            "question": "The noun form of ‘stormy’ is",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "stormed",
                "storminess",
                "stormful"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "cb57a8b98642406e89b7b86631588e9d"
        },
        {
            "question": "The adjective form of ‘wealth’ is",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "wealthiness",
                "wealthy",
                "unwealthy"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "805439fd748549cdbd55ba5bd91f65cb"
        },
        {
            "question": "The noun form of ‘compete’ is",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "competition",
                "competed",
                "competitive"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "76509621e4ac4a25b1fa317af8a2c71c"
        }
    ]
}